SPOOKY IN LOVE
EPISODE 9
INCOMING CALL
ELDEST SON
KANG MIN-HWAN
CEO CHEON YEO-RI
REINA HOLDINGS
MAJOR SHAREHOLDERS CHECKLIST
INVESTMENT COMPANY, INDIVIDUAL INVESTOR
REP, HAN SE-IN, SHAREHOLDING RATIO, 3
CONTACT IN PROGRESS…
HAN SE-IN SHAREHOLDER PROFILE
SHAREHOLDING RATIO: 3.0%
FATHER: HAN JEONG-EUP
(ARCHITECT, FOUNDER OF CHAEUM ARTRION)
PROSECUTOR MA GANG-UK
INTERNATIONAL ASSOCIATION OF PROSECUTORS'
31ST ANNUAL CONFERENCE
NOTICE OF ANNUAL CONFERENCE
AND SPECIAL SEMINAR
ELIGIBILITY AND SCHEDULE
SINGAPORE
12 YEARS AGO
CALL HISTORY
CKO CONSTRUCTION, HAN SE-IN, 3.00
FRIENDLY STAKE ACCUMULATION
STATUS AND TRENDS
INCOMING CALL
102♥
PAID LEAVE REQUEST FORM
MAY 8, 1991, 18:00
FEMALE, YEAR OF THE SHEEP
SPOOKY IN LOVE
REINA HOTELS, EXTRAORDINARY
GENERAL MEETING OF SHAREHOLDERS